<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--Designed to catalog and compare information about the vision/mission statements of churches in the area-->
<!--XML to be formed like a webpage (can/should be based on church's mission statement on their website, if applicable)-->

<!--source: https://www.facerie.org/our-vision-and-beliefs -->

<?xml-model href="simons_xml-03_relax-ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<!--still lots of errors with schema-->
<xml>
    <churchInfo>
        <name>First Alliance Church</name>
        <address>
            <ln1>2939 Zimmerly Rd.</ln1>
            <ln2>Erie, PA 16506</ln2>
        </address>
        <size data="large"/>
        <website exists="yes">https://www.facerie.org</website>
    </churchInfo>
    <section type = "context">
        <p>First Alliance Church has been ministering to Erie, Pennsylvania as part of the C&amp;MA
            for the last 125+ years.</p>

        <p>The US Alliance is part of a Christ-centered global movement more than 6 million strong.
            Our Acts 1:8 family—inspired by Jesus’ love and empowered by His Spirit—is passionate to
            bring the good news about Him to our neighborhoods and world.</p>
    </section>

    <section type = "content">
        <h1>OUR VISION</h1>
        <p special="highlight">To <point num="1">build</point>, <point num="2">equip</point>, and <point num="3"
                >mobilize</point> followers of Jesus so that all nations may know him, to God’s
            glory.</p>
    </section>
    <section type = "content">
        <h2 num="1">BUILD:</h2>
        <p>We function with the biblical understanding that God intends for all believers to grow in
            spiritual maturity, and that God uses our church in the growth process (1 Corinthians
            3:1–11).</p>

        <p>True spiritual growth only happens through the power of the Holy Spirit as people
            actively engage with the life-changing Word of God and actively engage with God in
            prayer. It is our desire for believers to move toward age-appropriate biblical literacy
            through expository preaching and teaching. We encourage relationships which are marked
            by mature believers coming alongside and discipling new believers. </p>

        <p special="tagline">THE FRUIT OF BUILDING IS CHRISTLIKENESS. </p>
        <p>This is evidenced when people see the world through a gospel lens and daily live out the
            gospel in real and tangible ways. Life decisions will be “gospel-shaped” and their
            entire lives will be an act of worship. </p>

        <h2 num="2">EQUIP:</h2>
        <p>We function with the biblical understanding that our church is responsible for providing
            the tools, training, and resources necessary to execute gospel mission and ministry
            (Ephesians 4:11–12).</p>

        <p>God has established certain roles in the church to prepare all believers for ministry. It
            is our desire for believers to identify their God-given spiritual gifts and be given
            opportunities to foster them. We encourage relationships which are marked by current
            ministry leaders coming alongside and developing new leaders. </p>

        <p special="tagline">THE FRUIT OF EQUIPPING IS SERVANTHOOD. </p>
        <p>This is evidenced when people move from being merely consumers to active participants.
            When they take what they have learned and put it into practice. </p>

        <h2 num="3">MOBILIZE:</h2>
        <p>We function with the biblical understanding that God calls all believers to mission, as
            commanded through the Great Commission (Matthew 28:18–20).</p>

        <p>It is our responsibility as a church to not only equip believers, but to prayerfully
            develop strategies and provide opportunities for them to go and do ministry in their own
            contexts and beyond! It is our desire to be a “sending” church where our members pursue
            intentional, sacrificial, and long-term relationships with unbelievers, both locally and
            globally, to love them like Christ and proclaim the gospel.</p>

        <p special="tagline">THE FRUIT OF MOBILIZATION IS WINNING SOULS.</p>
        <p>This is evidenced when believers go beyond the comforts of life to be the heart, hands,
            and feet of Jesus—and, by the power of the Holy Spirit, unbelievers become committed
            followers of Jesus Christ.</p>
    </section>
</xml>
